dumb crap primed and ready
don't suppose you'd like to trade this I
mean I'd have gotten my fists sooner if
it wasn't for those meddling kids
where did you hide your treasure you
could hardly have it on your person
treasure sure I know anything you're
talking about
you look like the kind of guy he could
use something blown up a candidate just
came to mind
I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in mm-hmm well
something out
I get cold just looking at you there you
should look somewhere else
you're just a no-good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror I
beg your pardon I consider myself a
freedom fighter misunderstood one
you hukum I'll cook him oh shut up you I
believe a Jake I'll pig fie saving they
told me the other day
all right oh oh oh be on my best
behavior try and stay out of single for
once
Oh be on my best behavior try not to get
us killed out there
ah remember that time we stole the crown
jewels
all hail King Jameson Fawkes the first
and Duke right what is your name anyways
me
[Music]
no Cookham
she is nice the Cavalry's here that's my
line think I could have a look at one of
those bombs of yours over my dead body
and I thought I was supposed to be the
comic relief
was i serious yes we know he's really on
top daily Oh back to the scrap heap I
could always count on you mate oh I knew
there was a reason I kept you around and
it wasn't the sparkling conversation
hi I'm the Ally wanna gets to kill the
big log